This video will introduce you to the main function of Kolo 2025.1, the seamless division.
In the past, if there was a flat color design on the fabric, it was necessary to cut and sew the sheets and then set them separately.
Now with the seamless division function, you do not need to cut the sheets again.
It is possible to separate each area, and thus apply color or texture like processing a separate fabric.
This is especially convenient for the design of a combination of various colors or textures such as needles or applications of different materials.
First of all, we will demonstrate how to create a seamless division line through an example file.
The seamless division is located under the multi-edged tool in the 2D tool bar.
After selecting the tool, you can draw a seamless division line by pressing the outside line of the board.
Please note that you cannot start drawing from the inside of the board.
The seamless division line can be created in the same way as the inner line.
By pressing multiple points to create any shape you want.
When drawing a straight line, press the Shift key to create a 45-degree support line.
To help you accurately draw a vertical line and a horizontal line,
or a 45-degree support line,
double-click on the line outside the board to finish.
If the board has a symmetrical link,
when creating a line on one side,
it will automatically create the same line on the other side.
It is suitable for boards with one symmetrical axis,
and boards with two symmetrical links.
The lines created in the 2D window will be highlighted in light blue,
making it clearly visible.
On 3D clothing, their appearance is the same as the inner line,
and the line is dark red.
If you want an asymmetrical design,
you can create a line with a symmetrical axis of a symmetrical board.
In this case, there will be no symmetrical duplication.
You can create an asymmetrical design with only a line on one side.
If you want to edit the end point,
you can use the edit board tool to edit the line section.
You can also create a curve line.
The creation method is the same as the creation of the inner line.
By pressing and dragging, you can create a straight line with a Beissel curve handle.
If you make a mistake,
you can also use the delete key to delete the point.
You can also press and drag the Ctrl key to create a curve point.
Thus, you can create a curve freely.
After creating all the lines,
you need to create a curve line on the outside of the board,
or on the other previously created non-divisional curves.
To complete the creation of the line section,
it should be noted that the non-divisional curve should always start from the closed shape.
Now let's modify the newly created non-divisional curve.
The modification method is the same as before.
You can use the edit board to modify the straight line on the Beissel curve.
You can also use other tools in the edit board tool group to edit.
For example, edit the curve point.
If you need to delete the non-divisional curve,
you can use the edit board tool to select the line and press the delete key to delete it.
You can also easily convert the internal line on the board
or the basic line to the non-divisional curve.
Select the loop outline tool,
stop the mouse on the internal line or the basic line you want to convert,
then right-click,
select the non-divisional curve shape in the list that appears,
this will immediately change the selected line to the non-divisional curve.
Using this function can make it easy for you to process the style you have decided to design
and you don't need to re-draw the line.
Next, let's use the fixed frame to create multiple non-divisional curves at once.
Use the edit board tool to right-click on the non-divisional curve,
click on the non-divisional curve frame,
this will open the dialogue box with the same options as the internal line frame.
You can enter the required number and distance in it,
which is particularly useful for pattern design or division and repetition materials.
Now let's apply different fabrics to the non-divisional curve we created.
Select the required fabric from the object window,
then drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
You can see that even if it is symmetrical,
it will not be applied at the same time when applying the fabric.
This is to give you more freedom in design,
you need to apply the fabric to two areas separately.
Of course, you can also use the adjustment board tool,
select the area and apply the required fabric for it.
Next, let's apply the fabric on the pants.
Use the edit pattern tool to adjust the fabric pattern.
Now let's simulate the clothing.
Because the physical properties of the fabric have also been applied to the fabric,
it can be realized to separate the fabric according to the non-divisional curve,
and simulate different physical properties.
The biggest advantage of the non-divisional curve line is that
when you modify the paper pattern,
the line section will also be adjusted.
For example, if you modify the outside line of the sheet,
the non-divisional curve line will automatically adjust the proportion of the outside line of the sheet after the modification.
When you are in the stage of frequent modification design,
this can make your work more convenient.
In order to save the trouble of modifying the inside line every time you modify a paper pattern,
of course, if you open the extension or subtraction function of the non-divisional curve line,
you can maintain the original extension direction.
As you can see, only this section is in the original state.
You can choose whether to turn on this function according to your needs.
Now I want to add a sticker to the position of the front seamless curve. The operation method is the same as before.
The seamless curve will not affect the display of the sticker.
The sticker looks very natural, as if there is no line.
The seamless curve line can be added and set its specific parameters like the internal line.
The seam is the same.
You can add it according to your needs.
The seamless curve is completed.
The seamless curve is completed. The seamless curve is completed.
So, the area where the Panel is set is not displayed in the hard новых window.
So, the area where the Panel is set is not displayed in the hard nuevos window.
Don't forget to set the coats妇k to the entire panel when you add a seamless curve line.
Also, if you open the file of 2025.1 and go to the second version in the previous version, the seamless curve line will be converted to the basic line.
END
Now let's learn the disrespect of this function fine by also paying attention to this point.
Free expression allows you to release the creativity of design clothing